

MIHAELA HABGOOD

447544833098 | mihaela_habgood@yahoo.com 12 Main Street, Failsworth, Manchester, Greater Manchester M35 9PD

Education

2019

CPD Certified Oplex Careers
Admin & Secretarial Skills Level
3: Admin & Secretarial

2012

Oracle University | Oracle
Global University
RightNow Cust Portal Design &
Contact Ctr Exp Designer Adm 1:
IT Service Design and Delivery

2012

Oracle University | Oracle
Global University
RightNow Customer Service
Administration Rel 11.11 TOD: IT
Service Design and Delivery

2012

Oracle University | Oracle
Global University
Oracle Application Express:
Developing Web Applications Ed
2: IT Service Design and Delivery

2011

Oracle University | Oracle Global University Oracle Database 11g: Administration Workshop I Ed 2 LVC: IT Service Design and Delivery

2009

BCS Iseb Qualifications |
Oracle Global University
ITIL Version 3 Foundation: ITIL

2009

Profile

Hard working, trustworthy, loyal, with a previous vast and varied expertise and work experience, multiple transferable skills, bilingual, punctual, pro-active, calm, self starter and results oriented.

Skills

Customer Technical Support Admin & Secretarial Skills Level 3 Bilingual: Romanian and English languages Full driving license IT Service Design IT Service Delivery IT Technical Support Incident Management Service Requusts / Ticket Management Major Incident Management **Problem Management** Escalation, KPIs, ITIL Windows, Linux System Administration Provisioning services Pro Active Monitoring Oracle Administrator **Oracle Systems** CRM. Oracle DBA Extremely organised Self-motivated Attention to detail Types at 70 wpm

Work history

05/2017 - Current

SASA Foods Ltd | Manchester, Greater Manchester Team Member

 Maintaining high standards of customer service during high-volume, fast-paced operations. Oracle University | Oracle
Global University
Enterprise Linux: Linux
Fundamentals Ed 1: IT Service
Design and Delivery

2008

IANLP | Bucharest, Romania NLP Practitioner International Association of NLP: Personal Development / Psychology

2007

Mind Master | Bucharest, Romania NLP Professional Start & NLP Professional Intensive: Personal Development / Psychology

1997

Emil Racovita | *Galati, Romania* GCSE

RQF Level 3 / SCQF Level 6-7 / CQFW Level 3. Overall standard of GCE Advanced (A) level / Scottish Advanced Higher / Scottish Baccalaureate / Advanced Welsh Baccalaureate

01/2016 - 05/2017

S.C. Aha Tools S.R.L | Bucharest, Bucharest Principle / Owner Owner of Escape Room Operator Business.

01/2009 - 12/2012

Oracle | Bucharest, Bucharest System Administrator

- Https://www.oracle.com
- Global IT Field Services: Design, deployment, testing and migration of teams into new platforms and tools.
- Oracle University QA: ProActive monitoring and quality assurance based provisioning services.
- Oracle University Global Support: Provisioning, Ongoing Incident solving and workflow improvement.
- Ticket / Service Request management, Incident Management, for External andInternal Customers (Oracle Staff, Oracle Trainers, Oracle Sites).
- 24X7 ROTA to cover AMER, EMEA and APAC.
- Scored in top 10% of employees in successful resolution of issues, exceeded KPIs.
- Identified and solved technical issues with a variety of diagnostic tools.
- Managed call flow and responded to technical support needs of customers.
- Provided base level IT support to non-technical personnel within the business.
- Installed software, modified and repaired hardware and resolved technical issues.
- Resolved problems with malfunctioning products.
- Remained up-to-date on the latest technologies and solutions applicable to company products.
- Activated accounts for clients interested in new services.
- Followed up with clients to ensure optimal customer satisfaction.
- Resolved customer issues in a clear, courteous and straightforward manner.
- Investigated and resolved customer enquiries and complaints in a timely and empathetic manner.
- Effectively communicated with and supported sales, escalated Service Requests to Problem Management Team.

01/2008 - 12/2009

Eco Corc SRL | Bucharest, Bucharest Consultant

 A time-determined project to promote and transition company's services and products in East and West Europe.

01/2007 - 12/2009

Diperia Vita Med S.R.L. | Bucharest, Bucharest Consultant

 Responsible with company's brand strategy and media image; design, deployment and maintenance of website and database; Network PCs and medical devices troubleshooting and upgrade.

01/2006 - 12/2007

Pro Casa Agency | Targoviste, Dambovita, Romania Manager Assistant

 Administrative and secretarial duties; design, deployment and maintenance of site and customers database;
 Company's PCs troubleshooting and upgrade.

01/2000 - 12/2005

Profesional M SRL | Galati, Galati, Romania Owner / Principle

 Others types of education; trained and certificated +1000 students in Fashion Modelling field.

References

Upon request.